Allahu Akbar Allahu Akbar La Elaha Ella Allah
La Elaha Ella Allah.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
We praise God and we bear witness that there is no god except the One God.
Today is the first day of a new year. It is January 1st, and I don't see a single person with a hangover in here.
The first day of the new year of 1988
is also the first day of the rest of your life.
And the Quran provides the ways and means of starting all over again, anytime you want to.
We can forget completely about the past and start as a totally new person beginning a totally new life.
The concept of repentance. Repentance: returning to God.
Being unaware for a while
and now deciding to return and be with God.
I have put
the theme of the new translation of Quran on the wall here
for you and I'm gonna read it
because I wanted to share it with you.
Well, before I read it, I'd like to say that finally we've discovered the secret of happiness,
the most elusive of all human searches.
The secret of happiness is in this
short theme here: Happiness is a quality of the soul, the real person, not the body.
Therefore, a body that achieves all the material successes it longs for: money, fame, power, good looks,
carnal satisfactions often belongs to an unhappy person. The real person's happiness depends totally
on the degree of growth, development and fulfillment of the real person.
This book, the Quran, maps the road to perfect happiness for both body and soul,
both in this temporary world and in the eternal Hereafter.
So, this is the secret of happiness.
And you've seen the video that we made couple of weeks ago.
And I mentioned in it Eddie Murphy
in his interview with Barbara Walters
and how he owns this big estate in New Jersey where he has his family. His mother see him successful.
He's got the success, the fame, the movies, the TV, millions of dollars, five cars, two Rolls-Royces, a Porsche,
a Mercedes, a Corvette, yet he said that he was not happy.
So, what does a human being want in this world?
Is this what... isn't this what everybody out there thinks they want?
The millions of dollars, the Rolls Royces, the Mercedes, the estates, the palaces and he's not happy. So,
this proves once again... this been proven over and over that material success does not bring happiness.
If the soul is shrunk and not fed and not nourished, there is no happiness.
This is the secret of happiness. Nobody can be happy unless the soul is nourished and develops and grows.
Just try not to feed your body for one day and see how miserable your body is.
Try for one day not to feed your body or give it water.
The soul is exactly like that if the soul is not nourished.
But in our dimension here, we do not feel the pain.
It is reflected in what Eddie Murphy told Barbara Walters that he was not happy.
It's reflected in that.
This is the secret of happiness.
A few weeks ago, they had the Barbara Hutton story on the TV and many of you saw it.
Same thing, wealth, fame, anything she wanted,
yet you saw her in the program trying to commit suicide.
This is a true story, how miserable she was,
the exact opposite of happiness. So, what does everybody out there want?
You want money, fame, good looks, success,
but then if the soul is not nourished, there is no happiness.
The nourishment for the Soul, God teaches us in the Quran, just like mentioned in the theme in here
that the Quran maps the road to perfect happiness.
And it starts the minute you wake up. We've been learning here from the Quran
that when you wake up in the morning, the first thing you say is
Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem.
Right there, it's a good snack for the Soul.
It's a bit of nourishment.
The minute you open your eyes in the morning, you say Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem. La Elaha Ella Allah.
There is no god except the One God.
The Quran teaches us specifically when you admire anything that belongs to you,
you must say: Mã shã Allah
This is the Arabic. You can say it in English. This is what God gave me in English.
Say Mã shã Allah. You admire your car, your children, your spouse, your house, anything that belongs to you,
and this invokes protection for your belongings
and it is nourishment for the soul,
because the soul is a piece of God.
And when you say Mã shã Allah, your soul grows,
another bit of nourishment.
You praise God. You Say Alhamdu Lillah.
Thank God or Praise God
when something good happens
when you finish eating.
When you start your car, you say Bism Allah and you...
When you start eating, you say Bism Allah
In the Name of God.
And when you finish, you say Alhamdu Lillah.
Thank God. Praise God
When you see something wonderful,
the sunrise or the sunset
or a flower
or a fruit, or anything God created, or a cute cat,
you say SUBHAN ALLAH.
God be glorified.
SUBHAN ALLAH. God be glorified.
Any time you think of God, because your soul is a piece of God,
your soul will be nourished.
Don't just eat the apple or the orange.
Think
who made this?
Where did it come from? Where did the apple come from?
The perfect flavor, the perfect sugar,
the perfect texture, the crunchiness.
Who designed this? Where did it come from?
It came from the air, by the way,
and the liquid from the soil.
This is where the apple came from.
It starts as a little ovary
and then it grows.
The leaves of the tree collect carbon dioxide from the air and link it together in chains.
The sugar is carbon: ccccc, six carbons make one small molecule of sugar.
So, the leaves of the tree, photosynthesis. You've heard the photosynthesis
and the energy from the sun
and the water from the soil.
This is it. This makes the apple
and all the other chemicals.
Don't just eat the apple to feed your body.
Eat the apple and feed you soul by saying SUBHAN ALLAH.
God be glorified.
Because the body, you're gonna throw away.
The soul is you
and you're gonna last forever.
The best nourishment of all is the contact prayer
making contact with God.
These are casual snacks,
Mã shã Allah (this is what has given me), Alhamdu Lillah (Praise be to God/ Thank God), Inshã Allah (God willing).
You should never say I'm gonna do something the next hour, or at 2 o'clock or tomorrow or next month or next week
without saying Inshã Allah, God willing.
You're gonna shock your American friends first but then they will get used to it and they will respect you later.
And you will nourish your soul, as you remind them and remind yourself.
Say Inshã Allah.
So, these are the snacks for the soul
and they may barely spare you misery
be it temporary or eternal Hell.
It might, but
the best nourishment is the five daily contact prayers.
These are specifically prescribed by God at specific times with specific utterances and specific movements.
It's a numerical code.
It's a combination that causes contact
with God.
Then, your soul really grows.
And like you heard on the tape, the other day,
the soul grows in leaps and bounds which makes nourishment a lot more crucial and a lot more important than your meals for the body.
because, ok, you're gonna give your body three meals today
how much would you grow today?
The children probably grow at a higher rate.
But what is the maximum you'll grow?
One pound?
Hopefully not.
But the soul, if there is a weight for the soul, you may grow by 10 tons.
The soul has a weight in the other dimension, not in this dimension.
In this dimension, I think, they determined the soul is one ounce.
They put a dying person on a scale
and they weighed him before he died and weighed him after he died.
And the difference was one ounce.
This is scientific research. They wanted to catch the soul scientifically
in the material world.
But in the other dimension, wow,
you know, when they go to the other dimension, they're gonna see the angels and the jinns and all the other creatures of the other dimension.
And one prayer, very easily, makes you grow by 10 tons.
10 tons. Iman, how many tons do you carry in your 18 wheelers?
80 tons? 80,000 pounds over 2,000 is 20 tons. 80,000 pounds over 2000 is 40 tons.
Yes, 40 tons, yes. OK. You can, you can load Iman's truck with just one prayer.
I don't think you'll forget this now.
So, this makes feeding, nourishing the soul all the more important.
In Sura 22
or is it 21? Let me
make sure so we can go and refer to it.
21. It says that the reckoning is approaching while the people are totally unaware.
21. The reckoning for the people is fast approaching while they are totally unaware, heedless. Reckoning of what?
It's calculating
how much you deposited in your account, how much growth you attained for yourself.
And you can't just wait and wait and wait and then try to feed a shrunken soul.
There's such a time where it's impossible.
You have to do it everyday. You have to do as much as you can.
This is what we're really here for.
The reckoning for the people is fast approaching.
That Day will come.
Sooner than you think.
Because life goes fast.
For the young people, it seems so far away.
The reckoning for the people is fast approaching while they are totally unaware heedless (21:1).
Did you hear all the hullabaloo and the parties last night for the bodies that they throw away?
They did nothing for the soul.
If anything, they did things against the soul.
It went into the negative.
The Health Department was distributing condoms to the bars, so they give the drinks and condoms.
I mean, what is this?
You can be sure most of it is not legitimate relationships.
I mean, Satan had a heyday last night.
And these are negative. The souls go into the negative.
It was on the news all day yesterday. You know don't forget; get your condoms.
[21:2] Whenever a new reminder comes to them from their Lord, they listen to it thoughtlessly.
I mean, you remind them that they're gonna throw away their body
and their soul is gonna remain forever
and will be assigned a rank forever on the Day of Eternity.
And they are thoughtless. They oh, sure. They're so unaware.
Their hearts are distracted.
Satan succeeded in distracting them.
And the wicked confide to each other: is he not just a human being like you?
They will not take anything from you, any advice from you.
They hate advice. They hate the Truth.
[21:3] Would you accept magic while you see?
Their hearts are distracted.
And in the second KHUTBA, In Shã Allah, I will... I think I discovered something I'd like to share with you
that will help us not to be distracted.
Tooboo Ela Allah. Repent.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
Praise be to God. I bear witness that there is only One God.
He has no partners.
We are a very very lucky generation.
In Sura 56, we are told that
the lower Heaven is gonna be relatively crowded.
It's gonna be full of all the children who died,
all the people who died before the age of 40
and adults who did not nourish their souls enough.
It's gonna be like the coach in the plane
be crowded.
First class Heaven,
will not be crowded, big seats, comfortable. They all go to the same destination.
You remember going in the plane and these people sitting in first-class looking at you like
haha, I'm in first class. I have a big seat.
And you go in there, squeeze in this coach in the plane.
You may get a seat that you just barely fit in it,
especially, if you are a little heavy weight like myself. You'll really squeeze in there.
So, the coach is gonna be very crowded.
First class, God says in Sura 56
that there will be multitudes of the early generations, which ours is one of them
and few of the later generations.
You know, God wills that this generation of ours witnesses a renewal of the message.
You know, the Christians have gone astray. They have been worshiping Jesus.
The Muslims gone totally astray worshiping Muhammad and the saints.
And the people forgot about God and all of a sudden, there comes into focus God Alone message
with this fantastic miracle that is coming to to enhance that.
I'm sure many many people thought of it and I have met a few of them
but they did not have the authorization or the power or this mathematical code in the Quran that points at God Alone.
19 means God is One, God Alone.
And this is our generation. You can be sure that subsequent generations will be fewer of the people.
I mean, here we are; we are pounding each other's head every day. Let's worship God alone. Let's worship God alone.
You're idol worshiping. I am idol worshiping.
You know, we are reminding. We are a lucky generation.
There will be multitudes of us, our generation, IN SHAA ALLAH, in first class,
in the High Heaven.
Now, the difference is much greater than first class and coach of the plane.
But then as, as the message, as they move further from our witnessing of the miracle,
we are witnessing the miracle before our eyes
and as they move further, there'll be less and less, according to Sura 56.
So, we are a very lucky generation.
And this brings to us more privilege.
I will not call it responsibility. I will call it privilege
to be much more careful, to do our five daily prayers, to observe God, observe His laws
make ZIKR continuously.
Well, this reminds me.
If you get distracted, the new ZIKR...
I was listening to the Quran the other day and the reader in a beautiful voice was saying
the part of Quran where God says do they think that I do not hear their secrets and their conspiracies?
Do they think that I do not hear their secrets and their conspiracies?
And when Moses and Aaron said we're afraid Pharaoh may kill us. God said don't worry. I'll be with you. I hear and I see.
And this inspired me, as I was going to sleep two nights ago to say God hears my secret
and my declarations.
God knows my secrets.
And this evolved gradually until I said
God is here in this room.
God is here now in this room. God sees me, hears me.
And this is what you have to visualize and materialize.
And it has a tremendous, great effect. I'm sure your soul will grow tremendously.
And if you had any devilish thoughts, they will go away.
You just visualize God with you. God is in this room, wherever you are.
God is here now. God is with me.
This is a new ZIKR.
God is teaching us.
And it will help you a lot.
It helped me.
And this is what I'm sharing with you now.
God is with me. God is in this room.
He is... see, as we talked now. God is in this room.
God is Omnipresent in every room, everywhere.
And personally with you as well as that ant out there by the roses.
God is with that ant.
God controls everything that the ant is doing,
how much food it gets.
God is with me.
God is here.
He hears my secrets,
what I'm thinking.
And this will help a lot.
The miracle,
I'll just give you a piece of news as to what I'm doing
since we're all in this together.
What I'm doing now is
I'm gonna give the mathematical miracle of Quran a lot of attention in the coming days and weeks, In shã Allah.
And what I'm doing is I'm making a generic video tape on the miracle.
Generic means that it will just have the facts in the video
and anybody can dub his or her own language on the tape.
So, I'm going, I'm going to do the English and the Arabic.
We're gonna have Mohtasham or Abdullah or both do the Turkish.
Gatut will do the Indonesian, Malaysian. Franchesco will do the Spanish.
We're gonna dig up somebody to do the Urdu, and so on.
Susan will do the Farsi and the French because she is good in both.
So here, so we're gonna have it in English, Arabic, Urdu, Turkish, Indonesian, Malaysian, Farsi, French.
Eric is going to do it in Swedish.
Eric Thornwall
So, we will also have these flashcards. These are flashcards
and I can have them by next week.
And they help a lot of people,
especially that there must be like 75% to 80% of the people who have a mathematical mental block.
You know, what's one plus one?
She doesn't know.
It's called the mathematical mental block.
A lot of people have them.
They're geniuses.
But these flashcards...
have to laugh a while.
The flashcard
makes it easy, so...
We're gonna edit this out.
Sometimes you get intoxicated.
This is called God's intoxication.
The smallest thing
you know, people who drank last night, think they were intoxicated.
And at first, the smallest things makes them laugh
Then, they wake up in the morning with a huge hangover.
And sometimes God's people get like that.
You know, the smallest things make them laugh out of control.
This is the title; it says Mathematical Miracle of Quran.
And this says these are all physical facts.
And this is the last statement before the actual facts.
The Quran is mathematically coded beyond the human intelligence.
This is Arabic and English, by the way.
We're gonna have them in nice-sized cards for everybody.
Here is...
This is another set, the last one, I promise.
It says the Quran's mathematical code is based on the number 19.
And here is fact number one.
You see how simple it is.
Fact number 1: opening statement of the Quran the Bismillah consists of 19 Arabic letters.
This is fact number one.
Fact number 2: The Quran consists of 114 Suras or 19 x 6.
Fact number 3: First revelation of Quran was 19 words.
Fact number 4: First revelation, the 19 words, are 76 letters, 19 x 4.
First revelation is 19 verses.
And it goes on like that.
Last revelation was 19 words.
So, they're all concentrated facts.
This is the quick summary.
And then what I will have after this will be
the pictures from the Blue Book, for example, where it shows Bism Allah Arrahman Arraheem, broken down into letters
19 letters
and then Gatut will say it in Indonesian.
These are the documentation of these facts.
These will take only like five minutes,
all of them.
And then so we come to fact number 1, the documentation for fact number 1, Gatut will say it in Indonesian.
The Bismillah consists of 19 letters, as you see.
And anybody can say it in any language.